欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
缇娜 瞧瞧你哟 姑娘
Oh, Tina, look at you, girl.
是啊 瞧瞧自己嘛
Yes, and look at you.
哎哟哟 还有我老公
Oh, oh- oh, - look at my husband. - Oh...
看着像个巧克力小点心
Looking like a chocolate snack.
你知道就好
You better know it.
我呢 是什么小点心
What kind of snack am I?
哇哦 你看起来是
Ooh, uh, you are looking like a...
葱油饼加老腊肉咸干酪
smoked gouda on a Triscuit.
-你知道就好 -是啊
You better know it. - Yeah.
恩 戴夫 你就穿这个去音乐会吗
·Mm. - Oh, Dave, that's what you're wearing to the concert?
天 白人真是什么都敢穿
Boy, white people get to wear anything.
至少这次他没露脚趾
Well, at least his toes aren't out this time.
看起来好长好怪
Looking all long and weird.
-嘿嘿 -哦
·Hey- hey. - TINA: Oh!
美丽的准辣妈来了
There's our beautiful mother- to- be.
抱歉我们迟到了
Sorry we're late.
我本来要穿别的裙子
I was gonna wear something else,
但我穿上的一刻 意识到我脱不下来了
but I grew out of it as I was putting it on.
哦 对
Ooh, yes.
戴夫 你不换衣服吗
Dave, you're not getting dressed?
该死 我已经换好了
Damn it! I am dressed.
卡尔文 感谢你帮我们弄到票
Calvin, thank you so much for getting us these tickets.
我们是托妮·布拉克斯顿的超级粉丝
We are huge Toni Braxton fans.
不用客气
Ah, you're welcome.
只要你们都记住
And just so you all know,
这算作是你们的生日礼物
this counts as everybody's birthday
和圣诞礼物
and Christmas gift.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你不算 宝贝 不
Uh, not you, babe. No...Oh.
欢迎来到这个社区 欢迎来到我们街坊
♪ Welcome to the block, welcome to the neighborhood ♪
欢迎跟我们做邻居
♪ Welcome to the hood. ♪
卡尔文 感谢你帮格罗弗也弄了张票
Calvin, thank you so much for getting Grover a ticket.
知道吗 我们给他听托妮·布拉克斯顿的音乐当胎教
You know, we played Toni Braxton for him in utero.
他的第一场演唱会也是她 真是太完美了
It is so perfect that this is gonna be his first concert.
他超激动的
He is so excited.
可是吧 他看起来一点都不激动
Well, damn, he doesn't look excited.
他一副穿着睡衣要去睡觉的样子
He looks like he's ready for bed.
格罗弗 别这样 你会喜欢的
Grover, come on. You're gonna love it.
这是你从小就听的音乐
This is the music you grew up on.
我喜欢她的音乐
I like her music.
我只是不希望自己的第一次演唱会
I just don't want to go to my first concert
是跟一帮老人家一起去
with a- a- a bunch of old people.
他说谁老了 谁他妈
Who's he calling old? Who the hell...?
好了 宝贝宝贝宝贝
Okay, babe, babe, babe, babe.
行 我这就给他一个上床睡觉的理由
Hey...you know what? No, I'lI give him a reason to go to bed.
听着 格罗弗 回家换条正经裤子
Now, Grover, go home and put on a real pair of pants.
马上
Now.
我的葱油饼从腊肉变成了火辣胡椒
My Triscuit went from gouda to pepper jack.
你确定这个样子可以出去玩吗
Now, are you sure you're up to going out like this?
确定 我想抓紧最后几周
Oh, yeah. I want to make the most
在达芙妮到来前好好嗨一场
of the last few weeks before Daphne arrives.
对 今晚的主题就是嗨
Yeah, and tonight is about fun.
千万别去想
No stressing about
一场改变火生的犬事件正在逼近我们
the massive, life- changing event that's looming over us.
但我可能会错过几首歌
I may miss a few songs, though.
这孩子在我膀胱上跳霹雳舞呢
This baby is breakdancing on my bladder.
别害怕 我已经标记出了
Ooh, fear not. I have mapped out
仲育馆的每个洗手间
every bathroom in the arena. Oh.
我还带了一袋你爱吃的
Mm- hmm, and I packed a baggy of that sliced ham
切片火腿
that you go crazy for.
嗯 就是这个味儿
Mmm, that's what I'm talking about.
是啊 拜托
Yeah, come on. Give me some...
他打包了一带火腿
He's got a pocket full of ham,
你们却来嘲笑我的卡其裤
and I'm getting grief about khakis?
马蒂 我看了好感动
Marty, that is so nice to see.
我知道你和考特尼只是朋友
I know you and Courtney are just friends,
但你这个怀孕搭档当得真帮
but you're such a good pregnancy partner.
随孩儿他爹 跟我一模一样
Just like I was. Chip off the old block.
是吗 我印象中的孩儿他爹不是这样的
Really? Cause that's not how I remember the old block.
好的 你觉得舒服不
Okay. Okay. Are you comfortable?
我应该让你舒服点才对
I'm supposed to make you comfortable.
你看我像舒服吗
Do I look comfortable to you?
别再碰我枕头了
And stop touching my pillow!
巴特勒先生 孩子要出生了
Mr. Butler, the baby's coming.
头要露出来了 看
He's crowning. Look.
你知道吗
Uh, you- you know what?
我没事 我不用了
Uh, I'm good. I'm good.
你们 你们看吧
You, uh, you, you do that.
毕竟 上过医学院的是你们
I- I mean, you're the one that went to medical school
你们比较懂
and everything.
卡尔文 卡尔文
Calvin. Calvin, Calvin, Calvin!
准备好摄像机
Get the camera readyl
好的 好的 嗯
Okay, okay. All right, um...
好的 呃 医生
Okay. Uh, doctor,
你觉得 既然你都在接生了
um, you...you think while you're down there,
能随手给我录个像吗
you could, you could get some footage for me?
我现在有点忙耶
I'm kind of busy right now.
护士 产钳
Nurse, forceps?
好吧 行
AlI right. Okay.
别担心 我来录 宝贝
AII right, I got it, baby.
-我来录 我们会看到的 -来吧
I got it. - We gonna see it. Ooh!
-我们这就来看看 -卡尔文
We gonna see it. ·Calvin! Calvin!
开录
Here we go.
天啊 这也太多血了
Oh, Lord, that's a lot of blood.
天啊
Oh, God.
我不行了
I'm going down.
他摔了个脑震荡
He wound up with a concussion.
我跟马尔科姆还比他先出院
And me and Malcolm got out of the hospital before he did.
听着 我本来都能出院了
Look, I was ready to go.
但你懂的 一旦你的保险能报销
But you know, when you got good insurance,
你就想多薅点羊毛
they want to milk it.
至少我一出院
As soon as I got out,
就承担起父亲的所有职责
I did all of the fatherly duties.
父亲的职责
Fatherly duties?
妈说你一块尿布都没换过
Mama said you ain't changed a single diaper.
我是没换过 我用买的
I didn't change'em, I bought'em.
各位 我要宣布一件事
Guys, I have an announcement to make.
为予感谢卡尔文帮大家弄到票
As a thank you to Calvin for getting us the tickets,
我请了位司机
I have hired a driver
送我们坐豪车去看秀
to take us to the show in luxury.
真棒
Well, all right!
特雷
Trey?
你请的司机是特雷
You hired Trey?
我这是支持黑人企业主
I am supporting a Black owned business.
特雷 你从哪弄来的这辆货车
Trey, where'd you get this van?
合法吗
Is it even legal?
当然合法 我在警察拍卖会上买下的
Of course it is. I got it from the police auction.
我天
Oh, God.
路上好堵
This traffic is terrible.
我们不会堵 宝贝
Not for us, baby.
瞧瞧警察在车里留了什么
Look what the police left in here.
特雷 这肯定不合法
Trey, I know that ain't legal.
车在纷纷给我们让路
People are getting out of our way.
等等 所以 爸
Wait, so, uh, so, Pop,
我出生时你真的昏倒了吗
you really passed out when I was born?
卡尔文 别担心
Calvin, come on.
你没什么好尴尬的
You have nothing to be embarrassed about.
你懂的 人在面对压力的时候
You know, sometimes we are just not
常常会掉链子
our best selves under pressure.
天啊
God,
还记得我们怀孕的时候
I remember when we were pregnant,
我们都累坏了
we were exhausted.
“我们” 你有啥可累的
We"? What did you do?
我家戴夫可积极了呢
Oh, Dave was very, very involved.
你要什么 要碎冰吗 要水吗
What do you need? Ice chips? Water?
我们 我们来深呼吸
Let's just, let's just breathe.
需要我唱歌吗
Um, want me to sing?
不要
No.
拒绝两次够说明问题了
Twice was enough.
亲爱的 你看起来很性感
Ooh. Honey, y- you look hot.
咱们把额头擦一下 嗯
Uh, let's mop that brow. Uh...
海绵
Sponge!
你没资格这么要求
You don't get to say that.
你非要事事跟我作对吗 唐娜
Must you fight me on everything, Donna?
-我明白 -这里该生了
I understand- it's go- time in here. Ooh.
不好意思 这个我没拍到
Damn it, you know what? I missed that.
你介意再从入口进来一遍
Do you mind taking your entrance again
最好再说一句“好戏上演“之类的话吗
and maybe saying something like"It's showtime"?
戴夫 够了
Dave. Stop it.
好了 亲 你看起来很紧张 这样吧
Okay, honey, you look tense. You know what?
我来放上我的特别混音CD
Let me put on my special mix CD.
托妮·布拉克斯顿的《顺其自然》
Toni Braxton's"Let It Flow. "
我说的对吗 唐娜
Am I right, Donna?
你还好吗
You doing okay?
你需要硬膜外麻醉吗 最后机会
You want an epidural? Last call.
要 要双份
Yes. Make it a doublel
嗯 珍玛
Uh, Gemma.
我们说好了要自然生产
We agreed that we would do this naturally.
我们改变主意了
We changed our mind.
我不想以子之矛攻子之盾
I- I hate to use your words against you,
但你曾说过 无论发生什么
but you did say, "No matter what,
别让我做硬膜外麻醉
don't let me get an epidural"
你说得对 说得对
You're right, you're right.
真抱歉 过来 亲爱的
I'm sorry. Come here, honey.
给我麻醉
； Give me the drugsl
马上给我上麻药 你听到了吗
I want the drugs right now! Do you hear me? l
上麻药 上麻药
Get her the drugsl Get her the drugsl
唐娜 给她上麻药
Donna, get her the drugs!
来看看 你还是可以看到
Check this out. You can still see
珍玛掐我脖子的指甲印子
where Gemma dug her nails into my neck.
但这些痛苦都是值得的
AlI the pain was worth it
因为我们有了个健康快乐的小男孩
because we got our healthy, happy baby boy.
我讨厌自己这一生
I hate my life.
至少他很健康吧
Well, he's healthy.
特雷 你不能走这条路
Uh, Trey, you can't go this way.
上面写了“请勿入内“
It says"Do not enter. "
这么写就是阻止你进去的
They just say that so you don't enter.
撞到交通了锥吗
Were those traffic cones?
但愿只是交通锥
I hope so.
VIP入口
VIP entrance?
确定我们要停在这里吗
Are you sure we're supposed to park here?
听着 只要离得够近 老娘不在乎
Look, I don't care as long as we're close.
这双鞋这么可爱 可不是走路用的
These shoes are cute, but they were hot made for walking.
呃 抱歉 特雷
DAVE: Uh, excu- excuse me, Trey.
特雷
Trey, uh...
你要是收到停车罚单
if you get a parking ticket,
-是你的责任 对吧 -不 全都是你的责任
- that's on you, right? - Oh, no, that's totally on you.
-好好读读合同吧 -什么
You should have- read your contract. - Well...
可是 咱没签合同啊
Well, there wasn't a contract.
该死
Damn it.
我的错 请在这里签名
My bad. Sign right here.
-我天啊 -你不用签
·Oh, my God. - You don't have to sign that.
你公司名字竟然是“跟你兄弟一起开车”么
The name of your company is Ride with Your Boy?
我把枪掏出来
♪ I pull up with the blick, blick ♪
我车停下 砰砰砰一片轰动
♪ I pull up, make your clique flip ♪
然后我开车离开
♪ I pull off in the whip ♪
轮胎发出刺耳的死磕
♪ And I skert Skert!
死磕
♪ Skert ♪
死磕 死磕
♪Skert...Skert!
天啊 小塞德宝炸场了
Hey, man, Lil Side Baby's killing it.
知道吗 我刚搜了一下小塞德宝
You know, I just googled Lil Side Baby.
他还演过《汉娜·蒙塔娜》里的史蒂夫
And it said he played Stevie on Hannah Montana.
-什么 -不 就是他 -他是演过
What? No, that is him. He did.
对 他因此获得了儿童选择奖
Yeah. He- he won a Kid's Choice Award for that.
那肯定是在他脸上纹身之前
That must've been before the face tattoos.
谢谢你 洛杉矶 晚安
LIL SIDE BABY: Thank you, LA. Good night.
小塞德宝 耶
CALVIN: Lil Side Baby! Yeah!
谢天谢地
Yes! Thank God.
-让托妮赶紧出场吧 -芜湖
·Let's get some Tonil- Whoo!
借过
Excuse me.
不好意思 借过
Excuse me. CALVIN: Hey.
你们买到周边了吗
You guys get your merch?
买到了 托妮·布莱克斯顿的T恤衫
Yes, we did. Toni Braxton T- shirts.
戴夫刚买了个小塞德宝的杯套
And Dave just had to get a Lil Side Baby cozy.
对 喝康普茶时用的
Oh, yeah. For my kombucha.
谁不喜欢凉凉的口感啊
Everybody loves a cold booch.
准备好迎接托妮·布拉克斯顿了吗
ANNOUNCER: Who's ready for oni Braxton?
-我天啊 -我懂 好兴奋啊 对吧
Oh, my Godl- I know, it's exciting, right?
不
No.
我水破了
My water just broke.
不会吧 你喝我的吧 拿着
Oh, no, you can have mine. Take mine.
不 马蒂
No, Marty.
我羊水破了
My water just broke.
你说啥 哦
What now? Oh!
-羊水破了 -羊水破了 -什么 什么 什么
Water brokel- Water brokel- What, what, what, what?
宝贝 你觉得她憋住一首歌的时间么
Baby, you think she can hold it for one song?
这票真挺贵的
I mean, these tickets were kind of expensive.
卡尔文
Calvin!
你觉得她能憋得住么
I mean, you think she could hold it?
-妈妈 -好的 走吧
Mama! Okay, come on,
-别这样 -大家让一下 拜托 都让开
come on. Let's move, people. Move! Out of the way.
我掏出一把亮亮的玩意儿
♪Ipull up with the blick, blick ♪
死磕 死磕
♪Skert, skert ♪
特雷 特雷 特雷
Trey, Trey, Trey, Trey, Trey. j Skert. ♪
快 咱们得走了
Come on. We got to go.
我们得走了 伙计
We got to go, man.
哟 演唱会结束挺快的哈
Oh. That was quick.
但钱还是按四个小时收哈
I'm still charging y'all for four hours.
拜托 考特尼羊水破了
Come on Courtney's water just broke.
不会吧
Aw, hell no.
看在你们是家人的份儿上
Because y'all family,
保洁费我给你们打八折
I'm gonna give you a discount on the cleaning fee.
-宫缩了 -好吧
Contraction... Okay,
咱们赶紧送她去医院吧
let's get her to a hospital.
抱歉 我们被堵在里面了
Sorry. We blocked in.
看到前面那辆保姆车了吗
See that van right in front of us?
那是托妮的车 她一时半会儿出不来
That's Toni's, and- she busy for a while. ·Aw.
特雷 我早说了不能停在这里
Oh, Trey, I told you we couldn't park here.
各位 我在给医生打电话
Guys, I'm trying to call the doctor.
你们手机都有信号吗
Does anybody have a signal down here?
没 没有
No. No.
不敢相信竟会发生这种事
I cannot believe this is happening.
知道吗 会没事的
You know what? It- It's going to be fine.
我要错过托妮·布拉克斯顿了
I'm missing Toni Braxton.
我是说 你们都听到了吗
I mean...can you hear that?
我很确定 这是《他不够男人》里的
I'm pretty sure that's the bass from
贝斯伴奏
"He Wasn't Man Enough. "
我最爱那段了
That's my jam.
好的 没事 放松下
Okay. Okay, just calm down.
好吧 我们时间很充裕
Okay? We have plenty of time.
没错 马蒂也是早产儿
Yeah, yeah. Marty came early,
当时情况也很顺利
and it all went smoothly.
咱俩对“顺利”的定义
You and I have very different
好像不太一样
definitions of"smoothly. "
真不敢相信你开一辆底盘这么低
I cannot believe you are taking me
的车送我去医院
to the hospital in a lowrider.
宝贝 我也是没办法呀
Look, baby, I couldn't help it.
这车我刚改装完 正试驾呢
AlI right, I'd just finished customizing this car
接到了你的传呼
and I was test- driving it when you beeped me.
啊 啊
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
缇娜 缇娜
Uh, Tina, Tina,
鞋不要放上来 宝贝
no shoes on the shag, baby.
怎么啦
What?
卡尔文 我要生了
Calvin, I am having a baby!
我知道 你能憋到我们到医院再生吗
Okay, but can you hold it till we get to the hospital?
什么
What?
你再敢问我一遍
Ask me that one more time.
再敢问我一遍
Ask me that one more timel
天 挡风玻璃上全是雾 稍等
Man, this windshield's all foggy. Hold on.
好吧
Okay.
出什么事了
What is happening?
抱歉 我按到开关了
I'm sorry. I hit the switches.
哥们儿 车真靓
MAN: Yo, sweet ride.
嘿 伙计
Hey, my man,
你喜欢这样的改装吗
you like what you see,
欢迎去卡尔文维修站体验
bring your car to Calvin's Pit Stop.
卡尔文
Calvin!
-我正生孩子呢 -孩子也得吃饭吧
I'm having a baby. - The baby's got to eat.
我天啊 疼
Oh, my Godl Oh!
卡尔文 卡尔文
Calvin! Calvin, Calvin,
我感到一阵推力
I'm feeling a lot of pressure.
要出来了 要出来了
Something's happening. Something's happening.
你能看看吗 你能看一眼吗
Can- can you look? Can you look?
看啊 脑袋出来了
Oh, look, it's a head.
哦天哪
Oh, God.
我不行了
I'm going down.
谁有正常一点的生产故事吗
Does anyone have a normal birth story?
-你们真的吓到我了 -好吧
Cause I'm starting- to freak out here. - Okay.
没啥大不了的 知道吗
It was no big deal, all right?
出来的只是你的头
It was just your head.
剩下的部分是到医院才出来的
The rest of you came out at the hospital.
好了 这样等下去没完没了
You know, this is taking forever.
戴夫珍玛 你们去找保安
Okay, Dave and Gemma, can you find security
让他们把这些货车先开出去
so we could get these vans moved?
-好 这就去 -好 这就去
Yeah, on it. - Yeah, on it.
好吧 我和马尔科姆去找急救医生
Okay, me and Malcolm will go find an EMT.
这里肯定有很多
I'm sure they're all over the place.
对对对 我去买玉米片
Okay, right. I'll go get nachos.
错
No.
特雷 你去把这些货车的司机找到
Trey, you'll go find the drivers for these vans
好让我们离开这儿
so that we can get out of here.
行 我敢说玉米片摊位旁肯定能找到
Right, cause I bet they up there by the nachos.
好了 各位 咱们还有时间
AlI right, guys, we got a little bit of time,
先来深呼吸 放松
so let's just breathe and relax.
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be just fine.
谢谢你 巴先生
Thank you, Mr. B.
好吧
AlI right.
这阵宫缩好疼
Huge contraction.
没关系 没关系 用深呼吸来引导
It's okay. It's okay. Just breathe through it.
嘿嘿呼 嘿嘿呼
Hee- hee- hoo, hee- hee- hoo. - Hee- hee- hoo, hee- hee- hoo.
你不是说宫缩间隔
I- I thoughtyou said
还很长吗
your contractions were still far apart.
之前是很长
They were,
但这孩子有点心急
but the baby doesn't give a...
孩子要生了 孩子马上要生了
The baby's coming! The baby's coming right now!
快来帮忙 马丁 过来
Help! Martin, come here.
你在千什么
What are you doing?
拜托 伙计 你能行的
Come on, man. You got this.
你知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
我不知道 课堂只教过
No. No, I don't. All they teach you
嘿嘿呼
in the class is"hee- hee- hoo. "
好吧
COURTNEY: Okay,
这孩子等不下去了
this baby wants out.
儿子 听我说
Son, listen to me.
你要勇敢面对你的恐惧
You got to step up and face your fears,
不然你会像我一样 后悔终生
or you'll regret it forever like I do.
你后悔吗
You do?
我当然后悔
Of course I do.
你妈妈当时那么需要我
Your mother really needed me,
而我却没能陪在她身边
and I wasn't there for her.
确切地说 我在她身边
I mean, I was, but
但我当时晕倒在地
I was laid out on the floor
瘫在车窗旁
or slumped against the car window
只能她来开车
while she had to steer.
但你可以做的比我强
But you can be better than me.
好吗 你能做到的
AII right? You can do this.
我知道你可以的
I know you can.
难道没人跟我说一句你可以的”吗
Isn't someone going to tell me I can do this?
-对 没人怀疑你 考特尼 -你可以的
Oh, yeah, nobody·doubting you, Courtney. - Oh, yeah, you can do this...
你势在必得
Like, you know you got it.
好的 咱们得找点毛巾
Okay, we're gonna need some towels.
好吧
AlI right.
但这里啥都没有 只有
Uh, we got nothing but, uh,
价值300美元的托妮·布拉克斯顿恤
$300 worth of Toni Braxton T- shirts.
好吧
Okay.
我天
Oh, boy.
她头已经出来了
She is crowning.
好吧
CALVIN: Okay.
我要不行了
Okay. I'm going down.
天呢 马蒂 别这样
Whoa, whoa, whoa...Marty, come on.
马蒂 别丢下我 好吗
Marty, stay with me, okay?
呼吸 嘿嘿呼
Breathe. Hee- hee- hoo.
嘿嘿呼
Hee- hee- hoo.
死磕 死磕 耶
Skert, skert. Yeah.
你们都做的很好
Keep going, y'all.
好的 都做得很好
Okay. All right, you are doing great.
-开始用力吧 -好的
Let's push. CALVIN: Okay.
-来 握住我的手 -好的
AII right, here. Take my hand. Okay, okay.
-握住我的手 -好的
Okay, just hold my hand. - Okay, okay.
开始吧
Here we go.
嗷呜 我的无名指啊
Ooh! That's my ring finger.
天 我快饿死了
I'm, like, starving.
小塞德宝把休息室的食物都吃光了
Lil Side Baby ate up everything in the greenroom.
谁会这么做啊
Who does that?
我天啊 托妮·布莱克斯顿
Oh, my God. Toni Braxton!
这不是我的保姆车
This is not my Sprinter.
这个女人在生孩子吗
And is that woman having a baby?
好 听着 事情是这样的
Okay, okay, okay. See, what had happened was,
我们的司机闯了几个交通锥
is that our driver ran over some cones,
然后就开到了艺人入口
and we came in to the artists' entrance,
我老婆穿着一双名牌鞋
my wife had on these designer shoes,
因为这种鞋不能走路
because she couldn't really walk in them.
你知道 不能穿着走长路
Yourknow, you can't really walk in them.
总之 我们就想 那车就停这儿吧
Anyway, we said, "Whoa, let's just go in this way. "
而且 没错 这位女士正在生孩子
And- and, yes, this lady is having a baby.
鲍里斯 你能帮忙
Boris, can you...can you help
把货车开出去吗
get these vans out of here?
哦 天哪
MARTY: Oh, my God!
露出脑袋了 各位
We have a head, people!
露出脑袋了
We have a head!
这样吧
You know what?
-咱们开生吧 -好的
- Uh- uh. Let's do this. - Okay.
好吧 你叫什么名字 孩子妈
All right, what's your name, Mama?
托妮·布莱克斯顿
Toni Braxtonl
不不 妈妈 不是我名字 你的名字
No, no, Mama. Not my name. Your name.
她叫考特尼
Her name is Courtney,
顺便说下 我俩都是你的铁粉儿了
and we are huge fans, by the way.
超铁的
I mean, huge.
谢谢喜欢
I- I appreciate that.
你得用力 考特尼 好吧
Now, you got to push, Courtney. All right?
孩子爸 准备好接生了吗
Daddy, you ready to receive?
是 托妮·布拉克斯顿
Yes, Toni Braxton.
数到三啊 一 二 三 用力
On three. One, two, three. Push!
我的手要折了 抱不了孙女了
Oh! I ain't gonna be able to hold my grandbaby.
各位 我们找到帮手了
Okay, guys, we found some help.
哦天啊 孩子出来了
Oh...my God, it's a baby.
是的 妈妈
It is, Mommy.
出来了
It is.
她好美 我们给她包起来吧
She's beautiful. Let's wrap her up.
好的 好的 来 包起来
Oh, good, good. Yeah, here we go.
哦 包在印着我头像的T恤里
Oh, in one of my T- shirts.
好嘞 我喜欢
Okay, I love it.
我的粉丝越来越年轻了
My fans are getting younger and younger.
噢 我的小达芙妮
Oh, my little Daphne.
你一定是孩子奶奶吧
I take it you must be the grandma?
是的
Yeah.
诶我操
Oh, damn.
你是托妮·布拉克斯顿
You're Toni Braxton.
这是托妮·布拉克斯顿
Th- This is Toni Braxton.
你好 托妮·布拉克斯顿
Hi, Toni Braxton.
你好 奶奶
Hi, Grandma.
考特尼 你已经生完了
Courtney, it's all over.
又可以正常呼吸了
Now you can breathe again.
正常呼吸
Breathe again.
我就知道你刚才
I see what you did
做了点什么
right there.
难以置信 给我接生的是托妮·布拉克斯顿
I can't believe Toni Braxton delivered my baby.
嗯 我呢
Um, hello?
你做得很好 爸爸
You did a great job, Daddy.
恭喜了 小弟弟
Hey, congratulations, baby brother.
孩子真漂亮
That's beautiful.
你好啊 托妮·布拉克斯顿
How you doing, Toni Braxton?
我叫马尔科姆 我是孩子叔叔
My name is Malcolm. I'm the uncle.
棒球甲级联赛教练
Division one baseball coach,
而且
and, uh...
单身
...single.
挺可爱
That's cute.
总之 很高兴认识你们
Anyway, it was nice meeting all of you guys,
恭喜你们啦
and congratulations.
我天
Oh, my God.
你看起来美呆了 托妮 她看起来很棒
You look fabulous, Toni. She looks great.
马尔科姆
Hey, Malcolm.
-在 -为你骄傲 孩子
· Yeah. - Proud of you, boy.
谢谢爸
Thank you, Pop.
你搭讪了托妮·布拉克斯顿
You took your shot at Toni Braxton.
-虽然没撩上 -没撩上
And you missed. - I missed.
-但你勇敢去撩了 -是的
But- but you shot. - Yeah.
天啊
Oh, my God.
她也太美了吧
She is so beautiful.
我可以一直抱着她
I could hold her forever.
你确实一直抱着
You have been.
给我 给我 给我抱抱
Yeah, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
好的
TINA: Okay, okay.
看这个小宝宝啊
Look at that little baby.
听着 格温
MARTY: Uh, look, guys?
大家伙儿
Guys, guys.
发音清楚些
Full words, please.
我们决定不用婴儿语
We've made the choice not to use baby talk.
跟婴儿说话么
To talk to a baby?
对 研究表明这样会延迟
Well, studies show that it can delay
孩子的语言能力
a child's language skills.
呵 你们这父母做得真没意思
Yeah, y'all gonna be fun parents.
医生说你明天就能回家了
So, the doctor says that you can go home tomorrow.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
当然准备好了 嗯
I'm so ready. Mmm.
-糟了 -怎么
Oh, crap. What?
-婴儿床还没搭好 -等等 没搭好
The crib isn't built. - Wait, it's not?
我爸本来要搭的
No, my dad wanted to do it,
但是我父母星期三才能过来
but my parents can't get here till Wednesday.
那我就先用摇篮吧
I guess Ican just use the bassinet.
不不不 不是摇篮的问题
Oh, no, no, no. It's not about the bassinet.
不能把孩子单独丢给你一人
You can't be with the baby alone.
马蒂 你得跟她一起去
Marty, you got to go with her.
但我的公寓超级小
In my tiny studio?
他要睡在哪儿呢
Where would he even sleep?
别担心了 你可以住在我们家
It's not a problem. You can stay at our place.
我们可以把婴儿床从你妈家搬出来
We can get the crib from Mom's house
放进那间空屋
and put it in the spare room.
那间空屋
Spare room?
你是说我的健身室么
You mean my exercise room?
我的健身器材放哪儿去
Where's all my gym equipment gonna go?
马尔科姆
Malcolm.
马尔科姆 听着 我们一直计划
Malcolm, look, the plan was always
把那个空房间改造成达芙妮的房间的
to turn the spare room into Daphne's room at some point.
这个计划我怎么不知道
I ain't never heard this plan.
好吧 那我承认这个计划有点问题
I see now the plan was flawed.
但是兄弟 你说我怎么办
Well, look, man, what do you expect me to do?
孩子一半儿是归我的
You know, I have half a baby.
我知道这话有点不合时宜
I hate to sound ungrateful,
但那间空房够放张婴儿床外加一张大床吗
but is the spare room even big enough for a crib and a bed?
你可以睡马蒂的房间
You can sleep in Marty's room.
我们不是一对儿 拜托
We are not a couple, man.
哦 得了吧
Oh, please.
好的 好的 听我说
Okay, okay. Look,
考特尼可以睡马尔科姆的房间
Courtney can go in Malcolm's room,
马尔科姆可以和我们一起住
Malcolm can come stay with us.
住哪儿 我的鞋帽间么
Where? In my shoe room?
听着 这只是考特尼父母没来前的权宜之计
Look, it's just until Courtney's parents get here.
对 但他们是会走的
Yeah, but then they're going to leave,
你们俩人还是会分住两栋房子里
and you'll be two people in two houses
毫无头绪地带着一个孩子
with one baby and no clue.
你们可都是火箭科学家啊
So, y'all rocket scientists.
俩人都抽大了吗
Have you been huffing the fumes?
爸 我以为这是三周之后的事
Daddy, I thought we had three more weeks.
你们都把宝宝弄哭了
Y'all made my baby cry.
来吧
Come on.
把她给我
Give her to me.
瞧瞧她啊
Look at her.
你还好吗
How are you doing?
是的
Yes.
瞧我 依然宝刀未老
Still got it.
你得教教我这招 爸
Okay, you have got to teach me that, Dad.
好了 别担心
Well, don't worry.
没人能完全准备好
No one's ever really ready.
我们会找到办法的
We'll all figure this out.
这需要全村人的帮忙
It takes a village.
各位 抱歉哈
Hey, guys, I- I'm so sorry.
咱们讨论过教父教母的事了吗
Have we discussed godparents yet?
不是给你们压力哈 但是
I mean, no- no pressure, but,
你懂的 我为此错过了音乐会
you know, I did miss the concert
她出生的那辆车也是我付的钱
and paid for the van that she was born in,
更不用说那件贵到离谱的
not to mention the very expensive
演唱会t恤了
concert T- shirts,
顺便说下 完全报废了
which, by the way, are a total loss.
但是 嗯
But, um
你听到那个声音了吗 那个烦人的声音
You hear that voice? That annoying voice?
那是你叔叔戴夫
That's your Uncle Dave.
最好现在就习惯
Get used to it.
他会一直叨叨个没完
It never stops.